Hello everyone!
Ooba Hana of Equal Love and
with Sen and Ikiwara
Otoshimari and
Akiko Taki.
Yes! Today's project is
Rizenku's 1st first attack!
Yay!
We have the King of Equal Love competition left!
There are now only 2 people left!
So there are two of us.
First offense and...
I'm the King of Ooba!
I played Tamamoto this time.
I played Tamamoto, too.
Otani, Noguchi, Otoshima, Takamatsu, Kiya
Yamamoto was me.
Wow!
The Six Kings.
Isn't he great?
Lao...
Takiaki is Hitomi.
Akiko has Morohashi.
We can't win anymore.
We're wiped out.
That's right.
Let's go for it.
Yes! Let's do our best!
We'll produce Akiko and do our best!
Let's do our best!
Akiko, let's do our best!
Question 1
What is Shoko Kiwaki's date of birth and blood type?
Rudimentary.
Wait a minute.
If I get this one wrong, the tour is over.
Eh, it could be bad!
I'm waiting.
I'm in trouble!
Oh, no!
Your blood type is a surprise.
What? It's not like that.
No, it's not like that.
Oh, wait.
Wait, wait, wait, wait.
Oh, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Oh, my God, this is really bad.
I'm so sorry if I squeezed you.
It'll be a surprise.
Then let's all try to figure it out together.
Ready?
How's that?
Oh, that?
Huh?
Wait a minute.
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
He's type A, even though he's a generalist.
What does that mean?
He looks serious, but he's actually rough.
Rough.
What?
You're kidding?
Let's see what you got right.
Yes, sir.
Okay, here's the correct answer.
July 9, 2001.
Oh, I'm so proud.
But that's not my birthday.
It fits. It fits.
I was just saying that you're a big girl, even though you're a type-A girl.
I'm always saying that.
I made a mistake.
Well, well, well.
It's only the first question.
First question.
Yes, yes, yes.
Score one?
A point?
Yes.
Zero.
Second question.
Go ahead.
In one word, describe Shoko Kakiwaki's personality?
Eh, about that.
How would you describe yourself?
What?
One word?
One word.
Wait, wait, wait. You mean you think it's hard?
You mean you think it's hard?
I mean, I'm thinking it, too, but I've been told that a lot.
Oh, I see.
I get it.
Oh, my God.
Do you have your desyllables on?
Do you have the dehyphenation on?
Can I say that?
Yes, I can.
Yes, it's desyllabic.
Oh, okay.
Oh, no, maybe not.
Is there another way to say it, too?
It's not a derailment.
Is it a derailment?
Oh, I don't know.
Well, it does say that.
But I can't remember what a derailment is.
Well, then, let's all come up with an answer.
Ready?
That's it!
Oh, not even close.
Yes, yes, yes.
Not at all.
Calm.
Energetic.
Active.
Yeah, I know.
I wasn't sure if you were active or not.
You said it was short.
I'm fine.
Like, "You seem calm.
Like, you don't seem nervous.
I thought too much of what they said about you being calm.
I was a little screwed up at the optimistic point.
We'll see next time.
Here's the next time
SERIOUS
Wow!
What's that!
That was a classic!
That's what Hana-chan said just now.
She's so serious, she's like a type A girl.
But isn't he calm and serious?
Calm.
Excuse me.
That's the closest I can get.
I'm serious.
Next question is here.
Shogo Akiwaki...
I'm feeling high right now. I'm going to shout it out.
Over!
I don't understand.
Stop saying "over.
Say what you're thinking out loud
I'm just yelling.
I'm not saying what I think.
Say what you're thinking out loud.
Aah! I'm not saying what I'm thinking
I'm saying what I'm feeling.
Aah!
Yes, sir.
Okay, bye.
I'll go first.
I'm feeling pretty pumped up right now.
Forget the high spirits!
Yes, sir.
I want to play the quiet game!
I'll do it.
You've got to be right.
He's talking to us.
You have it.
The correct answer is right here.
Here you go.
I'm a little nervous.
Wow!
That's amazing!
Hana-chan, that's great!
Hana-chan, you're right.
Wait, isn't this amazing?
When I thought about the situation of being interviewed by myself.
I thought you'd be nervous.
You've got to be realistic.
That's amazing.
You look like you're good at it.
Here's the next question.
What is the biggest mistake Shoko Kihashi has made in 2023?
Is it during the activities of the Ricola Club or other than that?
During Ricola Club activities.
Heh.
Did something happen?
But for now...
No one's mentioned it.
No one?
I haven't mentioned it anywhere.
Was he there?
Like, was he there?
Uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh...
I remember something.
I remember.
But I might have been in love.
I might have been in love.
Huh?
But if it wasn't this...
It's just...
No, it wasn't.
It wasn't that.
Okay, here we go.
Ready?
Yes, sir.
I was late for more than one rehearsal.
I got the meeting time wrong and was late.
I might have done that?
I might have.
I was a little clouded.
I had...
I have a cloud.
I got it.
I'm not going.
And then everyone saw me.
I'm so embarrassed.
Like I can't say it anymore.
I pointed out the wrong choreography.
For more than a year now.
Uh...
That's...
That's it.
This is it.
The correct answer is this one.
What I've done the most is...
I was at the rehearsal for "IKOI JOY 2023".
I made a one-hour mistake.
Well then...
You got it right.
You did it!
That's great!
But we hadn't started yet.
I was really pushing it.
So he was like, "Don't worry, it hasn't started yet.
He made me feel at ease, but...
But he was in a hurry.
That's what I meant.
Risa was right.
You did it.
That's great!
You did it!
She pushed it.
That's great.
Now, on to the next toy...
What is Shoko Hiraki's number one challenge in 2024?
What's that?
It's too likely.
I see.
Shuko is getting more and more like a toy.
What I want to challenge
Where's the pen?
where is the catapult?
What's that piroro?
What?
Where's the pen?
Oh, you're a camera-aholic.
Well then...
Okay, let's get to the answer.
Ready?
What do you think?
Oh.
Okay, then.
Oh, that's what I'm talking about.
Three points.
Oh, my God.
Oh, no.
Oh, no, no, no, no.
Oh, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Oh, no!
NAMMUSHI-
Catmouse
Catmouse.
Aggyaaaaaa...
Aggya-da-da.
But it seems to have fallen
He's down. - Rescue.
It's a rescue
Let's see the correct answer.
What would you like to challenge in 2024?
A provisioning ceremony.
Oh no!
I'm so close!
Oh, no!
That's it. That's not what I saw.
I wasn't thinking. I wasn't thinking.
I wasn't thinking about it. I wasn't thinking about it. I wasn't thinking about it at all.
That's great. We definitely won.
What's the score now? Two.
One?
But we're not there yet.
2 But here's the question.
3 Please write a song about Hakata no Tide.
What is Hakata no Tide?
Hakata no Tide.
Aaaaah!
Impossible!
How much is that in my head right now?
This is the problem I've been struggling with the most.
Troubled?
If I say the first letter, it's a little bad.
The first letter?
How much is the first letter?
The first letter is...
"Ta.
What?
Ah!
I was just thinking about that.
In my head.
Ta-ta-ta-ta-ta-ta-ta-ta-ta-ta-ta-ta-ta.
In order, in order, in order.
I'll go on.
Taisho Brabe.
Oh!
Oh no!
Tataki Mak
Ha-ha-ha!
I wasn't thinking.
Taki Mak
That's all I have too.
I'm Takiyaki Shoko.
Then I don't know.
The correct answer is here.
It's too hard.
Think, think, think!
I like tai shabu.
Oh, my God.
That's great.
I'll do less than one more question.
Just a little bit.
It's still great.
I thought I'd keep it simple, but I guess I'll have to go with tai shabu.
You're right, he said it's simple.
That's the funniest thing I've ever heard.
I love it.
I'm glad it's so simple.
So here's the next question
If you could switch places with any Ikonomi Joy member for a day, who would you switch places with and what would you do?
Oh, that's a tough one.
I think it's easy.
Easy?
I don't know, someone said something about it in an interview or something.
I think it was just the two of us.
Like, from now on.
That's a lot to start with.
Okay, let's get to the right answer.
Okay.
Yes, sir.
Ah!
They're all the same.
We're all the same.
We're all together.
No, no, no.
No.
Like this.
Yes.
Niew, follow me.
Float.
Okay, here's the correct answer.
Let's see...
The opening is easy.
I became Maika Sasaki and became a karaoke person
Huh?
Wait, wait, wait, it's not usually Maika.
Wait a minute.
I want to give 4.5 points to everyone
4.5 points
Yay!
That's great, but I know karaoke.
We split up, right?
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
I have a beautiful voice, too.
I made you sound beautiful, didn't I?
Okay, here's the next question.
If you call Marisa-san dead this year, what do you want her to fix?
Oh, no... I have so many things I want you to fix.
From a real person's point of view...
I'm not shocked.
But I wonder if I'll be able to fix this soon.
Can you fix it right away?
If I want to fix it.
I got one.
I think I got one of these.
Okay, let's get everyone's answers.
Okay.
Here you go.
Indecisive.
That's right.
Every time.
I'm sure of it.
I spill it all over my clothes.
Oh.
I'm just saying, the pen kind of stinks.
I'm serious.
It all fits.
They're all right.
All right, well, here's your answer, then.
Okay, here's the correct answer.
When we go somewhere together, please do a little more research.
Uhhh...
That's what I meant.
You're right, you're right.
I thought you'd answer.
Wow, she's already answered it.
I just said, "I want to go here.
That's all I did.
But I really want to fix it. I want to fix everything.
You know, looking into it.
That's what I'm talking about.
What do you have to say about today? You've been asking the guy at the store for about half an hour.
I asked the store owner when I asked.
I'm usually the one who decides.
Which one do you want to eat?
I do.
Next question.
What do you like best about Oobahana?
There are so many.
Least favorite part? Most?
Most? What's that?
I don't know.
Number one?
What?
Which one?
You can write them all down.
I'll write them all down.
Let's get the answers. Ready?
What do you like best about Oyobana?
She's cute!
Aaaaah!
Second, she makes me embarrassed many times.
Next, the fact that she is honest about everything.
Aaaaahhh...
Indeed.
Then, let's take a look.
Here you go!
The part where you are kind to everyone
Aah!
Yes!
I said a big one.
So many good things!
I'm so happy!
What again? Let's try a comment!
1.5
2.5?
What?
No? No?
Two and a half.
Ah!
Okay, final question! Go ahead!
Take a break.
What do you think Chiara will be doing when she's 30?
Uhhhhh?
What do you think she's doing?
Well, that's...
It's hard to say.
It's a little snarky.
It's not a swear word.
It's not swearing.
Maybe it's not an action.
What's going on?
The only fun way to answer that is to swear.
What's that?
I don't know.
It's like a path for Chiara.
No, it's not.
Like it's because of Chiara.
Not because of Kiara.
Ehhhh?
Simply imagine Kiara at 30 and see what she looks like...
Aah! I wonder what she'll be like.
I'll give you two points for that.
Finally...
Let's all come up with an answer together!
Ready?
Let's do it!
Yes!
Then, the most popular one is
I'll be the best mother in Japan.
Married, kids and all.
They'll be playing in the garden together.
Garden?
She'll be playing in the garden.
I'd love to be a mom again.
Okay, here's the correct answer.
The correct answer is here.
Kiara is 30 years old, has two kids, and is a mother of two.
Mother of two!
Mother of two?
But I really think that if I'm going to have kids, I'd rather have two.
Maybe we're on the same page there.
Mother of two.
Don't they look a little bit alike?
Yeah, I mean, the one with the two of them is a little bit different.
They're the closest.
I don't see the resemblance.
Two one's.
And you play in the yard with your kids.
Playing on YouTube.
Very popular.
Quiz is over.
We're done.
Let's review the points.
Yes, sir.
Three.
Two.
Hm
Climb up and say So, the 1st Hatsukyo is back again.
let's do it!
So that was the 1st first attack!
Yay!